<packageWizard size="500x500">
  <specs triplesFile="Resource">
    <spec name="Resource" 
          path="frames/resource.xml" 
          idtag="/dataset/identifier" 
          triplestag="/dataset/triple"
          displayNamePath="/dataset/title"/>
    <spec name="Table" 
          path="frames/entity.xml" 
          idtag="/table-entity/identifier" 
          relatedTo="DATAFILE" 
          displayNamePath="/table-entity/entityName"/>
    <spec name="Fields" 
          path="frames/attribute.xml" 
          idtag="/eml-attribute/identifier"
          relatedTo="Table"
          displayNamePath="/eml-attribute/attribute/attributeName"/>
    <spec name="Physical" 
          path="frames/physical.xml" 
          idtag="/eml-physical/identifier"
          relatedTo="Table"
          displayNamePath="/eml-physical/identifier"/>
  </specs>
  
  <frame name="Table"
         repeatable="no"
         dependsOn="Fields"/>
  <frame name="Fields"
         repeatable="no"/>
  <frame name="Physical"
         repeatable="no"
         dependsOn="Fields"/>
         
  <descriptions>
    <description name="InitialDescription">
      Welcome to the Morpho Package Wizard.  This wizard will assist you in 
      creating a data package consisting of your data file(s) and the information
      about your data file needed to track and use it more efficiently.  You will
      be asked to fill out a series of forms with information pertinent to your
      data as well as to show the wizard which data file you wish to describe.
      When the wizard is finished, your new data package will be opened in the
      Morpho Package Editor so that you can further manipulate it.  You will
      also be given the chance to upload you package to your Metacat server 
      (if you have one).
    </description>
    <description name="getData">
      Enter the path to the data file that you wish to describe. Click the 
      'Browse' button to browse for the file.  If you do not wish to provide
      a data file for this package leave the file field blank and click 'Next'.
    </description>
    <description name="Resource">
      Enter your contact information and basic data package information here.
      Scroll down to see more fields.  If a label is red, that field
      is required.  If a label is a button it is repeatable.  Click the button
      to repeat the element.  Whole groups can be repeated by clicking on the
      'Repeat' button at the top of the group.
    </description>
    <description name="Finish">
      The Package Wizard is now ready to create your new package.  The list 
      shows the items that the package will contain.  If you want to revise 
      your descriptions, click the previous button to go back.
    </description>
    <description name="Table">
      Data entered here should describe the tables in your dataset.
      If you have more than one table, you will be able to describe it later in 
      the Package Editor.
    </description>
    <description name="Fields">
      Enter information about the fields in your previously described table here.
      Only the name and definition of the field are required.  
    </description>
    <description name="Physical">
      Enter information about the physical configuration of a data object. 
      This generally is a detailed description of a text representation that 
      shows how the columns and rows of a table are represented, or simply 
      the name of a well-known binary or proprietary format 
      (e.g., Microsoft Excel 2000).
    </description>
  </descriptions>
  
</packageWizard>
